IVANNA CHUMATSCHKO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Phoenix. AZ

480-577-1857

ichumats22@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Full stack developer with experience in responsive website design and knowledge of server-side technologies. Well-organized and able to pick up new concepts quickly, I thrive in fast-paced environments with a variety of opportunities for creative problem solving. I am capable of completing projects independently or as part of a team, and hope to combine my social justice background and technical skills to improve conditions for underserved groups.

SKILLS

Bilingual (Eng-Spa)

· HTML

· CSS

Javascript

jQuery

NodeExpress

Handlebars

· React

MySQL

Firebase

MongoDB

Mocha

Chai

Git

Heroku

PROJECTS

Shelter Finder

https://github.com/Kbuchanan032/Project-3 https://p3-shelter-finder.herokuapp.com/

A website which helps users find nearby shelters with available beds and gives providers a place to manage space, track current guests, and keep a record of past guests.

Responsibilities: designed and created UI, routed data from UI to MongoDB.

Technologies: React, Javascript, CSS. MongoDB

Semi-Random Recommendations

https://github.com/AeroAtlas/Project2Beta3 https://project2beta.herokuapp.com/

Recommendation generator for movies, TV shows, and games based on user selected criteria and data gathered from two API's: The Movie Database (TMDB) and Rawg.

Responsibilities: designed and created UI Technologies: Handlebars, Javascript, CSS

EXPERIENCE

Remote Service Specialist • Agency Resource Solutions

July 2018 – Present

 Increased productivity in independent insurance agencies by creating custom processes for streamlining service tasks.

Office Manager • Sherwood Insurance Agency

May 2016 - July 2018

 Reduced onboarding time and improved compliance to company and industry standards through the development of training materials.

Political Affairs Intern • The Borgen Project

January 2018 - May 2018

 Augmented awareness and engagement of congressional representatives in support of foreign development aid.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer Certification • University of Arizona

September 2019 - March 2020

Bachelor of Science in Justice Studies • Arizona State University

September 2013 - May 2018

Dean's List (Fall 2013, Fall 2017)

Scholastic Diploma • Higley High School

August 2010 - May 2013

 Active member of Student Council and National Honor Society. Graduated with honors (4.0 unweighted GPS) a year ahead of schedule.